# Lauren Chen Digital Marketing Specialist



## **OBJECTIVE**

Digital Marketing Specialist with 4+ years of experience in online marketing, branding, and business strategy across music, media, and entertainment industries. Skilled in evaluating financial needs and implementing multi-pronged digital strategies that increase revenue and drive brand growth.

## **RELEVANT SKILLS**



## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

#### TRIANGLE MUSIC GROUP, New York, NY

Digital Marketing Specialist, September 2019-Present

- Manage digital sales and streaming accounts to improve brand positioning and growth
- Source and develop new strategic partnerships, social engagements, and advertising opportunities that generate new revenue streams
- Collaborate with internal departments to execute national advertising campaigns, plan global digital distribution, and re-deploy a 1M+ consumer sales and marketing database

# **MOMO SOFTWARE, New York, NY**

Digital Marketing Associate, June 2017-August 2019

- Worked with management to develop and apply digital marketing plans with a focus on driving acquisition and conversion
- Devised and implemented robust digital acquisition plans, ensuring precision in financial reporting, budgets, and forecasts
- Increased conversions by 15% from paid sources (PPC, Grant, Display, and VOD)
- Enhanced conversion rates by 12% via A/B testing landing pages for a better performing conversion funnel

# **KINGSTON DIGITAL, New York, NY**

Marketing Intern, June 2016-May 2017

- Helped research, write, and edit blog posts for Kingston's website
- Determined relevant keywords and entities for pages using Semrush, Ahrefs, and Page Optimizer Pro
- Gathered and analyzed data from social media PPE campaigns

# **EDUCATION**

#### **NEW YORK UNIVERSITY, New York, NY**

Bachelor of Arts, Communications, May 2017

Honors: cum laude (GPA: 3.6/4.0)



# Dear Job Seeker,

If you want to move your career forward, the Advanced resume template is for you.

Its sans-serif font, contact information icons, and eye-catching skills section make it great for applying to jobs in tech or data science.

Consider the Advanced resume template if you want to work in social media management or data analytics.

If you're still struggling to write your resume, here are some free resources to help you put together a resume that shows employers you're the right person for the job:

- · Free Resume Builder
- · How to Write a Resume
- Resume Samples by Industry

Once you have a great resume, pair it with a convincing cover letter using our matching 2022 cover letter template. Here are a few resources to help you write a cover letter that gives your application the boost it needs to land you an interview:

- Cover Letter Builder
- How to Write a Cover Letter
- · Cover Letter Examples by Industry

Best regards,

**IMPORTANT:** To delete the second page, right-click on the page and click "Delete Rows"

The Resume Genius Team